Guide to the Harold K. Boyd Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Harold K. Boyd papers
1907-1980
1955-1980
SC0278
Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs.
2 Linear feet
Office files of Harold Boyd, consisting of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, publications. Subjects include student conduct, legislative council, fundamental standards commission, and general office operation.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Office of Dean of Student Affairs, 1982.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Office files of Harold Boyd, consisting of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, publications. Subjects include student conduct, legislative council, fundamental standards commission, and general office operation.
Access Terms
Boyd, Harold K.; Stanford University. Dean of Student Affairs.; College students.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Papers
  - Correspondence, 1969-74 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1977 January – June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1977 July – December (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1978 January – September (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1978 October – December (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1979 January – May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1979 June – September (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1979 October – December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1980 January – March (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1980 April – June (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous and undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Boyd, Annual Report, July 18, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Boyd, Annual Report, July 17, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Student Conduct Legislative Council [SCLC]: agenda and minutes, Jan. – May 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SCLC: communications Jan. – April 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - SCLC 1969-70: legislation (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SCLC 1969-70: pending legislation (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SCLC 1969-70: minutes (Dec. 1969-May 1970) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - SCLC 1969-70: comments and correspondence (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - SCLC 1969-70: miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - SCLC 1970: agenda and minutes (Dec. 1969-June 1970) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SCLC 1970: communications (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - SCLC 1970: communications (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - SCLC 1970: penalty code (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - SCLC 1970: charter of 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - SCLC 1970-71: correspondence (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - SCLC 1970-71: background information (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SCLC 1970-71: minutes (Nov. 1970-May 1971) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - SCLC 1970-71: legislation (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - SCLC 1970-71: information on rules and regulations (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Unit Heads meetings, 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Unit Heads meetings, 1977-76 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Unit Heads meetings, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Unit Heads meetings, 1974-73 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, 1907-45 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, 1951-54 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, 1955-59 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, 1960-61 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, re liquor, 1957-62 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, re liquor, 1957-62 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, re liquor, 1962-63 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fundamental Standard Commission, re liquor, 1962-63 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - USE [United Stanford Employees] Strike 1974: policy memos (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - USE Strike 1974: operations center (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - USE Strike 1974: announcements (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - USE Strike 1974: correspondence and notes (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - USE Strike 1974: clippings #1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - USE Strike 1974: clippings #2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - USE Strike 1974: clippings #3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - DIAL (campus info service) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - DOSA Assumptions and Beliefs 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Grievance procedure for staff (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Intro to Stanford for Black Freshmen (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ROTC: clippings, 1968-70 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ROTC, memos, clippings, etc., 1967-70 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Stanford-Palo Alto Branch, NAACP (rough draft of a statement, n.d.) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Sub-committee on Academic Standing, 1977-79 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - White Paper on Richard W. Lyman, the Leading Candidate for Stanford's Seventh President, 1970 [no author cited] (Box 4, Folder 18)